<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Practical 3</string>
    <string name="article_title">About Kay</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Kay By Katrina</string>
    <string name="article_text"><b>Kay Beauty</b> by Katrina Kaif is the latest celebrity makeup brand to come out of Bollywood.
\n \n “As a person, I’m very demanding of myself. Kay Beauty has been created with this same rigour, asking a very demanding question – how can we get more out of makeup? The answer that the collection offers is a unique formula of makeup products that are long-lasting and ultra-glam, and cares for your skin,” says Kaif on her push to create a label that resonates with millennials. “Each product is  infused with ‘kare’ ingredients so that you can indulge in makeup without any guilt. It was also very important for me that the collection was versatile enough to cater to different skin tones, ages, and emotions. With the range of shades and buildable formulas, every woman can find their look. I’ve taken all the knowledge I’ve gained in my career and put it into these products. I hope that they give you the tools to explore your creativity and celebrate your own unique idea of beauty.”
        \n \n The launch collection will feature seven lip, eye, and brow products to create three international beauty trends – the 3D Lip, Sultry Eyes, and Natural Ombré Brows. The products that help create these trends are the Matteinee Lip Crayons, Matte Action Lip Liners, Maestrobe Metallic Lip Toppers, Kohl Star 24 Hour Kajal, Ink Artist Gel Kajal, High Drama Smoky Kajal and the Brow Studio Eyebrow Definer Pencil.
        \n \n The label stands on the three principles (also a play on Kaif’s initials) – Kolor, Kover, and Kare . Kolor represents the colour cosmetics with eyes, lips and nails; Kover and Kare, set to launch soon, will include high performance face products and nourishing ingredients respectively.
        \n \n Pricing:

The lip crayon comes with 24 shades and costs Rs 799.

The lip pencil comes in 12 shades and costs Rs 550.

The lip topper comes in 6 shades and costs Rs 699.

The kajal range comes from Rs 250 to Rs 599.

The eyebrow pencil comes in 3 shades and costs Rs 599.
    </string>
</resources>